Guil Sa,

Front-end developer, American/Brazilian, 32 years old Graduated in Advertising & P.R. from CUNY guilsa001@gmail.com | guilsa.github.io Tel: +1 (650) 296-6692

Overview

Guil is a front-end developer from Rio de Janeiro. He has six years of experience managing cross-functional B2B projects with both small and Fortune 500 clients in traditional and agile consulting environments.

Skills

HTML 5, CSS 3, Sass, BEM, Bootstrap, jQuery, React, Redux, ES5/6, Ruby, Sinatra, Git, Github, Sketch, Photoshop.

Experience

SELF EMPLOYED

Freelance Full-Stack Developer

<u>VouAtras.com</u> - similar to Ripoff Report. Includes creditcard processing, email notification and Trello integration for inbound lead tracking.

Interview Sidekick - CMS to conduct interviews.

Converted Sketch mockups into reusable React components (rating, tab, list, among others) which take in raw data and return user-interfaces.

<u>Cloudfarmer</u> - Responsible for frontend in React. Earn money by renting cloud storage space popularized by decentralized storage networks like StorJ.

HE:LABS

Agile Evangelist (DEC 2013 - OCT 2014)

Project managed over six Ruby on Rails applications using agile. Scope prioritization, user flow sketching and sizing user stories with planning poker. Qualified leads, monitored strategy and drove \$150K in revenue.

AUNICA, IGNITIONONE, MULLENLOWE

Project Manager / Digital Strategy (AUG 2008 - JUN 2013)

Fortune 500 online user-acquisition project management. Planning, selling, operations, tracking, reporting and analytics. Direct clients included CenturyTel, Kumon, General Motors and Isobar Brazil (projects for SKY and FIAT), among others.

Education

City University of New York - Bachelor in Public Relations & Advertising (2003-2007)

Courses

Dev Bootcamp (2015)

Codeschool - Try jQuery (2015)

Codeschool - JavaScript Road Trip 1-3 (2015)

Codeschool - JavaScript Best Practices (2015)

Certified ScrumMaster (2013)

Adobe Omniture SiteCatalyst Advanced (2012)

Project Management, ESPM SP (2012)

Work

www.vouatras.com
http://bit.ly/1t4inGx
https://github.com/guilsa/react-weather-app
http://falae.herokuapp.com
https://github.com/guilsa/cloudfarmer-landing-page
https://github.com/deluxe-pig/cloud-farmer (new contributor as of July 25)

